var QAList = [{
    question: "1. What does 'NaN' stand for in JavaScript? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: Negative and Number",
        b: "B: Not a Number",
        c: "C: No Associated Number",
        d: "D: Never a Number"
    },
    correct: "b"
},
{
    question: "2. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "3. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "4. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "5. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "6. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "7. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "8. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "9. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "10. What does the modulus operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
}
];
